bcbg.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy & Security

BCBG Max Azria Group, LLC. ("BCBG") is committed to respecting your privacy and recognizes your need to protect personal information that you share with us on our websites. Our goal is to adhere to the principles set forth in this Privacy Policy, which complies with applicable laws and regulatory standards.

These specific terms apply to the process and the use of personal data collected within the framework of any order placed from countries outside of the United States.

BCBG has hired Borderfree, Inc. (“Borderfree”) to enable shipping to 100 countries and territories. Please note that International purchases will be subject to Borderfree’s Terms & Conditions and Privacy Policy available through the links below:

Terms & Conditions: [_**http://www.Borderfree.com/terms**_](http://www.borderfree.com/terms)

Privacy Policy: [_**http://www.Borderfree.com/privacy**_](http://www.borderfree.com/privacy)

For questions regarding shipping outside of the United States, please contact BCBG Max Azria at [_guestservices@us.bcbg.com_](mailto:guestservices@us.bcbg.com) or 877.707.2224 in the United States or 972.421.9851 for International customers, seven days per week, 9:00 A.M. – 9:00 P.M. CT Monday through Friday, and 9:00 A.M. – 6:00 P.M. CT Saturday and Sunday, except when closed in observance of the following holidays: New Year’s Day, Easter Sunday, Memorial Day, Independence Day, Labor Day, Thanksgiving Day, Christmas Eve Day and Christmas Day.

## POLICY UPDATES

BCBG may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Whenever we make a change, we will post the updated policy on our websites. We recommend checking this section on our websites frequently to view the latest updates.

## PERSONAL INFORMATION

"Personal information" means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including but not limited to, first and last name, home or other physical address, email address, phone number, and payment information. In general, you can visit our websites without revealing any personal information.

## THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

#### Registration

During the registration process on BCBG’s website, you are asked to provide certain information, such as your name, mailing address and/or zip code, country, email address, phone number, birth date or year and/or password. Providing this data about yourself is entirely voluntary, but enables you to derive more benefit from BCBG’s website.

#### Communications

If you contact BCBG in any manner whatsoever, we may keep a record of such correspondence. For example, if you report feedback or an issue with BCBG’s website, we may collect such information in a file specific to you.

#### Log Files

Like most standard website servers, we use and maintain the information that we obtain from and/or through your browser on our server logs. This information can include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider ("ISP") and other data. We may use this information to analyze trends, administer the website, detect fraud or other types of abuse and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We may associate this information with your personally identifiable information to resolve technical issues, support security for our users and/or take action on any activity that may violate the Privacy Policy.

## WHAT WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION

BCBG is able to collect your personal information when you use our websites. This can be done only when you voluntarily submit such information on our websites. We use such information to display contents and products that may be of interest to you and to personalize your online experience. From time to time we may share such information with our business affiliates and third parties. All third parties that we share personal information with are contractually obligated to maintain the confidentiality of your information. We may also disclose your personal information under court orders or other legal requests.

Whenever you provide us personal information, you agree to BCBG using such data to deliver marketing material such as promotions, new merchandise or contests and sweepstakes to your email or physical mail address. If you choose not to receive such marketing material, you may explicitly opt out by doing so on our websites.

Your personal data collected by BCBG is used to:

  * Operate and improve BCBG’s website, services and offerings available through BCBG’s network
  * Personalize the content and advertisements provided to you
  * Communicate with you and respond to your inquiries
  * Share information with third parties, such information being covered by a nondisclosure agreement
  * Conduct research about your use of BCBG’s website
  * Help offer you other products or services that may be of interest

## CONSENT TO BCBG PROCESSING YOUR PERSONAL DATA

By providing data to us for the purposes of creating your account or adding any additional details to your BCBG profile, you are expressly and voluntarily accepting the terms of the Privacy Policy. You have the right to withdraw your consent to BCBG’s collection and processing of your data at any time, by changing your settings, or by closing your account, but please note that your withdrawal of consent will not be retroactive.

## BCBG COMMUNICATIONS

You can change your email and contact preferences at any time by logging into your account and changing your settings related to your email notification choices. If you wish, you can also opt out of receiving promotional emails by clicking on the "[ _ **unsubscribe**_](http://www.bcbg.com/en/email-preference?b=bcbg)" link. Please be aware that you cannot opt out of receiving service messages from BCBG.

## AFFILIATES AND BUSINESS TRANSITIONS

BCBG may share your information with its affiliates that are subject to privacy policies that protect your personally identifiable information from disclosure to third parties in a manner similar to this Privacy Policy. In the event that BCBG (or its parent corporation) goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition, liquidation or sale of all or a portion of its assets, our users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Members may be notified of any such business transition via email and/or notice on BCBG’s website.

## THIRD-PARTY OFFERS AND ADVERTISING

BCBG allows other companies, such as its marketing partners and affiliated companies, to offer their products and services to you, to register you on their websites, or to communicate with you about their products and services at a future date, through BCBG’s website or by email. Whether or not you decide to participate in such an offer is up to you.

As noted above, we may use your information to provide you with advertisements that are targeted to your specific needs and interests. These advertisements link directly to third-party websites. BCBG has no control over the content or privacy policies of such websites, and therefore we encourage you to review such content and policies prior to submitting any personal information to them. We share certain aggregate information, such as demographic information and the number of times its users have viewed an advertisement, with our third-party advertisers.

BCBG may allow certain companies to display advertisements on its website. Some of these ad networks may place a persistent cookie on your computer. Doing this allows such advertisers to recognize your computer each time it sends you an online advertisement. In this way, ad networks may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw its advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. BCBG may share certain non-personally identifiable information about you, such as your gender, age or zip code, with ad networks to help them deliver more relevant advertisements through their ad networks. BCBG does not have access to or control over the cookies that may be placed by these parties on your computer, and has no control over these parties' privacy policies or information-collection practices.

Google Analytics. Some or all of the BCBG Sites make use of Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. The BCBG Sites may also make use of other Google Analytics for Display Advertising features, including Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting and/or the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration. We are required by Google to disclose the following information to you in our Privacy Statement in connection with our use of any Google Analytics for Display Advertising features on the BCBG Sites:

  * You may opt out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising or customize Google Display Network ads by using the Google Ads Settings page. You may also prevent your data from being collected and used by Google Analytics by opting out through the use of the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on.
  * If the BCBG Sites make use of the Google Analytics for Display Advertising Remarketing feature, BCBG will use such Remarketing feature to advertise online and third party vendors, including Google, may show BCBG ads on sites across the Internet.
  * BCBG and third party vendors, including Google, may use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to (a) inform, optimize and serve ads based on a user’s past visits to the BCBG Sites, and/or (b) report how your ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to the BCBG Sites.
  * Data from Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting may be utilized by BCBG to help recognize and understand user preferences, to make improvements to the BCBG Sites, to choose content and advertising to display to you, and for other business purposes that will allow BCBG to better serve you.

## BROWSER "DO NOT TRACK" SIGNAL

Although our websites currently do not have the technology to recognize the various web browser Do Not Track signals, we do offer our customers choices to manage their preferences that are provided in the previous sections above. To learn more about browser tracking signals and Do Not Track please visit [_**http://www.allaboutdnt.org/**_](http://www.allaboutdnt.org/).

## PROTECTING CHILDREN

We take special care to protect the safety of children in accordance to the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998. While our site is a general audience site, we do not permit children under the age of 13 to register or purchase any products. We also do not collect or solicit personal information about children under the age of 13.

## COOKIES

To improve your shopping experience, our websites use "cookies", which is a feature that stores a small amount of data about your usage of our websites. Generally, we use cookies to keep track of what is in your online shopping cart and also to save your password so you don’t have to enter it each time you visit our websites. Please note that cookies do not contain any of your personal information. If you prefer to not use cookies, you can simply do so by disabling the feature on your web browser.

## SECURING YOUR INFORMATION

BCBG understands the utmost importance of protecting the personal information that you share with us. As such, we practice a combination of technical, physical and administrative security controls that are designed to safeguard your information against unauthorized use. Your personal information will only be used for business purposes and will only be accessible by a limited number of BCBG employees.

At the same time, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information to the best of our ability, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of information you transmit to our websites.

## STORAGE TERMS

BCBG applies the following storage terms:  
Information uploaded by you is stored for a period of six (6) months after you delete this information, or delete your account; it being agreed that you can delete your account at any time. If you do not log in to your account during a period of two (2) years, your account will be deleted automatically.

History and logs: stored for a period of six (6) months after the history item or log event was created.

Cookies: cookies used on the Site shall have a maximum lifetime of one hundred (100) days.

## HOW YOU CAN ACCESS OR CORRECT YOUR INFORMATION

#### Data Choices

BCBG provides you with ways in which you can modify your personal information. In order to change such information, please log in to BCBG’s website and go to the "My Account” section and enter any desired changes. Please be aware that even after your request for a change is processed, BCBG may, for a time, retain residual data about you in its backup and/or archival copies of its database.

#### Closing Your Account

You can disable your account by contacting BCBG Max Azria at guestservices@us.bcbg.com or 877.707.2224 in the United States or 972.421.9851 for International customers, seven days per week, 9:00 A.M. – 9:00 P.M. CT Monday through Friday, and 9:00 A.M. – 6:00 P.M. CT Saturday and Sunday, except when closed in observance of the following holidays: New Year’s Day, Easter Sunday, Memorial Day, Independence Day, Labor Day, Thanksgiving Day, Christmas Eve Day and Christmas Day. If you close your BCBG account, we will remove your name and other personally identifiable data from our publicly viewable database. If you close your account, we have no obligation to retain your data, and may delete any or all of your account data without liability. However, we may retain certain data contributed by you if BCBG believes it may be necessary to prevent fraud or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally identifiable data. BCBG may also retain and use your data if necessary to provide the services to other users. Similarly, data you have shared with others, or that other users have copied, may also remain visible. BCBG disclaims any liability in relation to the deletion or retention (subject to the terms herein) of data or any obligation not to delete the data.

#### Right of Access

In BCBG’s network, you are entitled to access your personal information and to have it amended, updated or deleted, where such information is incorrect, incomplete or outdated.

You may exercise this right at any time by sending a request in writing to:   
Legal Department   
BCBG Max Azria Group, LLC   
2761 Fruitland Avenue   
Vernon, CA 90058

BCBG will answer to your request within two (2) months from its receipt, provided that this request is complete, accurate and encloses a stamped envelope with your name and address.

You may also, on legitimate grounds, object to the processing of your personal information. Such objection may, however, prohibit BCBG from providing the requested service.

## CONTACT US

If you have any questions regarding this privacy statement, please contact us at:

Legal Department   
BCBG Max Azria Group, LLC   
2761 Fruitland Avenue   
Vernon, CA 90058
